### **James Ahn**

portfolio / jamesahn.co

ux/ui designer Jamesahn0717@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/james-ahn (236)-512-9610

# summary of qualifications

UX Design	HTML	Photoshop	Teamwork
UI Design	CSS	Illustrator	Problem Solving
Prototyping	Python	Premiere Pro	Time Management
Figma	InDesign	Lightroom	Self-Motivated

<sup>1</sup> years + of key experience in the travel industry, combined with a solid academic background specializing in user experience

### experience

#### Business and Design Mentor - Starterhacks at University of Waterloo

Jan 2020

Helped out students participating in the Starterhacks with possible ideas and how to execute them with a business mindset. With a business and design background, I was able to give some tips that I learned in the real world and how it can be used in their projects

#### **UX/UI Design Intern** - Tugolo

May 2019 - August 2019

Re-designed Tugolo's entire website using Figma to make it a more interactive and user friendly experience for its users. I worked with another designer and three developers that brought our designs to life. I focused more on the mobile designs as it was an essential part for Tugolo's target group. I started off with wireframes and moved to high fidelity models, user testing them to other workers and gaining valuable comments

#### **UX/UI Designer** - Tastebuds

Jan 2020 - present

Currently envolved in launching a startup and helping design for it. I am making adjustments on the current interface to give it a more simple and clean look. After these adjustments, I went out to ask for user feedback and modify it accordingly

#### education

#### Honours Global Business and Digital Arts - University of Waterloo

Sept 2017 - April 2021 Waterloo, ON

**Exchange Program** - Singapore University of Technology and Design

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019 Singapore

## activites & interests

Snowboarding Camping Hiking Travelling

Photography Videography

#### Snowboarding

Participated in the snowboarding club in my high school and went to provincials and won 3rd place boys snowboarding and 1st place in mixed snowboarding

#### **Travelling**

Went on exchange to Singapore and travelled to 5 different countries, adding count to the 21 countries I've travelled to

Continously expanding my knowledge through experiencing different cultures

<sup>2</sup> years + of prototyping and design sprints for quick ideas

<sup>3</sup> years + of working in Figma with teammates and efficiently get work done with them in an effective pace